[
  {
    "Option4": "Cumilla",
    "Option3": "Dhaka",
    "Answer": "Dhaka",
    "Option2": "Rangpur",
    "Option1": "Mymensingh",
    "Question": "What is the capital city of Bangladesh?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Urdu",
    "Option3": "Hindi",
    "Answer": "Bangla",
    "Option2": "English",
    "Option1": "Bangla",
    "Question": "What is the national language of Bangladesh?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Six",
    "Option3": "Two",
    "Answer": "Six",
    "Option2": "Ten",
    "Option1": "Seven",
    "Question": "How many seasons does Bangladesh normally experience?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Six",
    "Option3": "Two",
    "Answer": "Six",
    "Option2": "Ten",
    "Option1": "Seven",
    "Question": "How many seasons does Bangladesh normally experience?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Taka",
    "Option3": "Dollar",
    "Answer": "Taka",
    "Option2": "Rupee",
    "Option1": "Euro",
    "Question": "What is the currency of Bangladesh?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Padma",
    "Option3": "Meghna",
    "Answer": "Buriganga",
    "Option2": "Jamuna ",
    "Option1": "Buriganga",
    "Question": "On which river Dhaka is situated?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Myanmar and Nepal",
    "Option3": "India and Myanmar",
    "Answer": "India and Myanmar",
    "Option2": "India and Nepal",
    "Option1": "Nepal and Bhutan",
    "Question": "Bangladesh is bordered by two countries.Which ones?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Asia",
    "Option3": "Europe",
    "Answer": "Asia",
    "Option2": "South America",
    "Option1": "Africa ",
    "Question": "On which continent is Bangladesh located?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Other",
    "Option3": "Buddhism",
    "Answer": "Islam",
    "Option2": "Hinduism",
    "Option1": "Islam",
    "Question": "What is the main religion practiced in Bangladesh?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Tram",
    "Option3": "Toboggan",
    "Answer": "Rickshaw",
    "Option2": "Elephant",
    "Option1": "Rickshaw",
    "Question": "Which of these is a common mode of transport in Bangladeshi cities?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "1988",
    "Option3": "1971",
    "Answer": "1971",
    "Option2": "1975",
    "Option1": "1952",
    "Question": "What year did Bangladesh finally become independent and gain the name it has today?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Cuckoo clocks",
    "Option3": "Coffee",
    "Answer": "Textiles",
    "Option2": "Cars ",
    "Option1": "Textiles",
    "Question": "Which of these is a main export of Bangladesh?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "CPU",
    "Option3": "Mother Board",
    "Answer": "CPU",
    "Option2": "Graphic Card ",
    "Option1": "Memory",
    "Question": "Which of the following is the processing unit of the computer?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Drafts",
    "Option3": "Spam",
    "Answer": "Drafts",
    "Option2": "Sent",
    "Option1": "Inbox",
    "Question": "Which of these folders in Gmail will contain the emails which are composed but not yet sent?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Football",
    "Option3": "Hockey",
    "Answer": "Kabadi",
    "Option2": "Kabadi",
    "Option1": "Cricket",
    "Question": "What is the national game of Bangladesh?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Cricket",
    "Option3": "Hockey",
    "Answer": "Poetry",
    "Option2": "Politics",
    "Option1": "Poetry",
    "Question": "Kazi Nazrul Islam is Associated with?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "64",
    "Option3": "96",
    "Answer": "64",
    "Option2": "69",
    "Option1": "68",
    "Question": "How many districts are there in Bangladesh?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "Tianjin",
    "Option3": "Wuhan",
    "Answer": "Wuhan",
    "Option2": "Shanghai",
    "Option1": "Beijing",
    "Question": "The first case of novel coronavirus was identified in?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "2018",
    "Option3": "2021",
    "Answer": "2019",
    "Option2": "2019",
    "Option1": "2020",
    "Question": "When was COVID-19 first reported?"
  },
  {
    "Option4": "1",
    "Option3": "0",
    "Answer": "0",
    "Option2": "7105",
    "Option1": "5369",
    "Question": "What is the right answer: 7*51*0*255"
  }
]